<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Facebook Status</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="admob_interstetial_ad"></string>
    <string name="menu_home">My Home</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="title_activity_quote">ActivityCaption</string>
    <string name="my_favorites">My Favorites</string>

    <string name="about_notice">আপনার মনে স্বাভাবিক ভাবে প্রশ্ন আসতেই পারে আমি কেন Bengali caption for fb dp ব্যবহার করব? তাই তো ?
এর সহজ উত্তর হল, আমরা দৈনন্দিন জীবনে চলার পথে প্রতিনিয়ত অনেক কিছুই অনুভব করি এবং প্রতিনিয়ত বাস্তব আভিগতা অর্জন করি। যে অভিজ্ঞতা গুলি আমাদেরকে প্রতি সেকেন্ডে সেকেন্ডে নতুন কিছু শেখার জানার জন্য বাধ্য করায়।
হতে পারে এই অভিজ্ঞতা গুলি নিজের জীবনে ঘটে চলা ঘটনার সারঅংশ। আবার হতে পারে এই অভিজ্ঞতা গুলি অন্যের জীবনে ঘটে যাওয়া ঘটনার সারাংশ।
কিছু মানুষ তার জীবনে ঘটে যাওয়া কিছু সুখ, দুঃখ ,সফলতা ,বিফলতার গল্পগুলি Bengali short cation for fb রূপে রূপে প্রকাশ করে যা দেখে বা পড়ে আমরা মনোরঞ্জিত হয় , কিন্তু কোথাও না কোথাও ওই মানুষগুলি আমাদেরকে কে গোপন ভাবে কিছু বার্তা দিয়ে থাকে। যা আমরা অনুসরণ করে আমাদের জীবন আরো সুন্দর করে গড়তে পারি। তার জন্য আমাদের বিভিন্ন জায়গা থেকে কিছু মহান ব্যক্তির বাণী যা Bengali caption আকারে প্রকাশ করা হয় </string>
    <string name="privacy_notice">Privacy Policy

Allbangla apps built the সেরা প্রোফাইল পিক ক্যাপশন । Photo Caption Pro app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Allbangla apps at no cost and is intended for use as is.

This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.

If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at সেরা প্রোফাইল পিক ক্যাপশন । Photo Caption Pro unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

Information Collection and Use

For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that I request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.

The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app</string>

</resources>
